# Aviva I. Drozdinskyte (Drozdin)

# **Junior Full Stack Developer**

Herzliya | 058-778-0217 | dro.aviva@outlookl.com Github | LinkedIn

### **SUMMARY**

An innovation-driven professional with prior experience in software sales and market development now studying Full Stack Python and Data at Developers Institute.

A strong communicator with a natural curiosity for technology and a willingness to learn.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages & Technologies: CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, Python, Django, API/JSON,

PostgreSQL, SQLite

**Workflow**: Jira, Trello, monday.com **CRM**: Salesforce, Hubspot, Copper

## **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

## CarboFree / Github

(In collaboration with Igor Kazak & Adam Azani)

A website educating people about CO2 emissions and how their food choices affect it, by showing a real-time calculation of the carbon emissions that would be produced per kg/product.

- Built Website structure using Bootstrap to ensure quick and easy navigation.
- Utilized JavaScript to store relevant product data and display it in relevant product categories.
- Used JavaScript to calculate the data and display the calculation end-results in a graph in real-time.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Market and Business Development Specialist**

UK, DACH & CEE 09/2018 - 01/2020

Freelance

- Specialised in B2B SaaS and multichannel Marketplaces
- Developed key-accounts and partnership channels resulting in 120% growth across channels
- Developed and implemented strategies relevant to each country's culture and standards

## **B2B Business Development & Project Manager**

Herzliya, Israel

Israel Advanced Technology Industries (IATI)

01/2018 - 10/2019

- Identified and developed new opportunities and partnerships resulting in new international business ventures.
- Co-ordinated over 100 B2B Meetings between VCs and Israeli Startups
- Advised on business development from foreign relations perspective

### SAP / SAP B1 Recruitment Consultant

London, UK

Washington Frank International

10/2016 - 12/2017

- Generated Net Sales: approx. ~210K EUR
- Increased sales by renewing key-accounts and partnership channels.
- Took on responsibility for 30+ accounts in the DACH region.

### **EDUCATION**

## Full Stack Development, Python and JavaScript program

Tel Aviv, Israel

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

01/2020 - 04/2020

BSc Econometrics
London School of Economics and Political Science

London, UK 2013 - 2015

# LANGUAGES

English - fluent, German - fluent, Russian - fluent, Lithuanian - fluent